NAVAS CIFUENTES JONATHAN G.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Fullstack web developer, focused on providing professional technical solutions complying with software quality standards as well as the use of current technologies.

I have more than 4 years of experience as a software developer and in the last 2 years I have been working as a Freelance which has allowed me to code from web pages to robust enterprise systems.

I'm very interested in topics related to clean architectures, TDD, mobile application programming, i'm constantly updating my knowledge with online courses.

Experience -

Fullstack Developer - Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Design and development of a corporate website for a gastronomic coach "Ricardo Rivadeneira" in Ecuador using technologies such as Html, Css (UIKIT), Js, Php and Php-

Design and development of a professional website for the advertising agency "Pc Creativa". I used technologies such as Html, Css (UIKIT), Js, Php and PhpMailer

Freelance Developer - Feb 2020 - Present

Design and development of a web platform (SADGEC) for the monitoring and control of compliance with recommendations of the Comptroller General of the State. Which includes modules of report management, control of personnel and positions of public officials for government entities for the company "Planet-It".

Redesign and development of a platform for the sale of practical theoretical courses of martial arts for the company Zen-Sei. I used technologies such as Html, Css (UIKIT), Js, Php, PhpMailer. I also implemented the Paypal payment gateway for the purchase of course coupons.

Design and development of a web platform (SACVI) for the management of vacation licenses in governmental entities for the company "Planet-It". I used technologies such as Html,Css (Bootstrap 4.5) - AdminLte, PhpMailer, Mysql database.



Contact

www.ionathan-navas.com

+593 982329901

info@jonathan-navas.com https://github.com/jonathannavas

nttps://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-gabriel-navas/

Education

Universidad de las Fuerzas Armadas ESPE

Software Engineer Oct 2014 - Sept 2021

Certiprof

Scrum Master Professional Apr 2021

Howard Institute

English language proficiency Sept 2011

Skills

Front-end

Html

Css - (Uikit, Materialize, Bootstrap)

Javascript - React Js

Back-end

Javascript / Node js / Express JS (API REST, JWT) Java / Springboot Php

Databases

MySql

Firestore

MongoDB

Cloud Services

Heroku

Firebase

Mongo Atlas

Control Version

Git

Github